Guide to the Samuel Stark Film and stage stars: photographs, 1911-1969
Department of Special Collections
Stark, Samuel, collector. Film and stage stars: photographs,
1911-1969
MSS PHOTO 171
Stark, Samuel, collector.
9.5 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
The collection includes some 1,246 names are represented, many of these with more than one photograph. The bulk of the dated photos are between 1915 and 1940, though there are many more recent that are undated.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Samuel Stark, 1969.
Provenance
Originally formed part of the Stanford Libraries' Theater Collection.
Collection Scope and Content Summary
Some 1,246 names are represented, many of these with more than one photograph. The bulk of the dated photos are between 1915 and 1940, though there are many more recent that are undated.
Access Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Motion pictures--United States--History.; Theater--United States--History--20th century.; Photoprints.; Theater Collection.
Collection Contents
- George "Bud" Abbott and Lou Costello (1943) (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Aaymes, Rick (see Vera-Ellen file) (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Abel, Walter (6) (1936) (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Abram, Will R(autographed to "Harry and Min [?]"), (1916) (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Adams, Jimmie (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Adams, Maude (3) (1932) (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Adler, Larry (4) (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Adler, Luther (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Adoree, Myra (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Adoree, Renee (7) (1923, 1928, 1929), (2 o.s., 1 signed) (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Adrian, Iris (2) (1934) (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Aherne, Brian (11) (1933, 1936) (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Albertson, Frank (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Albertson, Lillian (2) (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Albiin, Elsy ("Forbidden Rapture") (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Alexander, Katherine (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Alexander, Ross (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Allan, Elizabeth (5) (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Allan, Maud (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Allen, Fred (3)(1938, 1940) (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Allen, Gracie (10)(1933, 1935, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Allen, Judith (1933) (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Allister, Claude (1927, 1949), (28-includes bio) (3 o.s.) (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Allison, May (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Aloma, Harold (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Alonzo, Alicia (4) (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Amaya, Carmen (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Ameche, Don (9) (1936,1937) (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Amos and Andy (6) (1925) (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Annabella (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Anderson, Agnes (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Anderson, Judith (3) (1936, 1939) (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Andres, Keith (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Angel Heather, (1 o.s.) (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Angelus, Muriel (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Angelin, Margaret (autograph photo, 1918) (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Apollon, Dave (3) (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Arbuckle, "Fatty" (Roscoe) (2)(1932) (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Arden, Eve (3) (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Arden, Mary (Box 1, Folder 40)
- "La Argentinita" (3) (autograph photo, 1929) (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Arkin, Alan (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Arlen, Richard (1929-36), (12) (Box 1, Folder 43)
  (1 o.s.)
- Arliss, George (6, 2 autograph) (1926) (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Armstrong, Robert (1939) (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Arno, Sig (2) (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Arnold, Dorothy (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Arnst, Bobbe (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Arnold, Edward (7) (1930, 1936, 1937, 1939) (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Arthur, Jean (25) (1927, 1930,1931, 1935, 1936, 1937, 1939), (1 o.s.) (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Ash, Sam, (1 o.s.) (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Asquith, Ruby (2) (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Astaire, Fred (15, 1 autographed to Mrs. Chandler, 1915) (1915, 1934, 1935, 1936, 1940?) (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Asther, Nils (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Astor, Mary (19)(1932, 1935, 1936), (1 o.s.) (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Auer, Mischa (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Austin, Gene (autograph photo) (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Autry, Gene (3) (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Ayres, Agnes (autograph photo) (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Ayres, Dudley (3)(1929) (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Ayres, Lew (4) (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Aznavour, Charles (4) (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Baclanova, Olga (3) (1942), (1 o.s., signed) (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Baer, Max (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Bailey, Frankie (7, 1 autograph)(1921, 1922, 1924) (Box 1, Folder 65)
- Bainter, Fay (2) (1932, 1937) (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Baker, Benny (1936) (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Baker, Phil (1 o.s., signed) (Box 1, Folder 68)
- Balanchine (Box 1, Folder 69)
- Ball, Lucille (8)(1936,1937) (Box 1, Folder 70)
- Ballew, Smith (5) (Box 1, Folder 71)
- Bancroft, George (9) (1928, 1933, 1934), (1 o.s.) (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Bancroft, Edna G(1934) (Box 1, Folder 73)
- Bankhead, Tallulah (12, 1 autograph) (1932, 1933) (Box 2, Folder 74)
- Banky, Vilma (4) (1929) (Box 2, Folder 75)
- Bannerman, Margaret (2) (Box 2, Folder 76)
- Bara, Theda (6) (Box 2, Folder 77)
- Barnes, Binnie (3)(1936) (Box 2, Folder 78)
- Barrett, Edith, (1 o.s.) (Box 2, Folder 79)
- Barrett, Judith (1939) (Box 2, Folder 80)
- Barrett, Vince (Box 2, Folder 81)
- Barrie, Mona (Box 2, Folder 82)
- Barrie, Wendy (6)(1935,1937,1939) (Box 2, Folder 83)
- Barriscale, Bessie (autograph) (Box 2, Folder 84)
- Barry, Mr. & Mrs. Jimmie (autograph) (Box 2, Folder 85)
- Barrymore, Diana (Box 2, Folder 86)
- Barrymore, Ethel (8)(1928,1932,1946) (Box 2, Folder 87)
- Barrymore, Mrs. Georgia Drew (mother of John, Lionel & Ethel) (Box 2, Folder 88)
- Barrymore, John (27, 2 signed, to Joe Laurie and Frankie Bailey)(1930,1931,1934,1935), (2 os, 1 signed to David Starr Jordan) (Box 2, Folder 89)
- Barrymore, Lionel (13)(1932,1935) (Box 2, Folder 90)
- Barthelmess, Richard (12, 1 autograph)(1933,1935) (Box 2, Folder 91)
- Bartholomew, Freddie (25) (1935,1936,1937) (Box 2, Folder 92)
- Barton, James (1935) (Box 2, Folder 93)
- Bates, Blanche (3, 1 autograph) (Box 2, Folder 94)
- Baum, Vicki (signed by VB to "Frank B, Riley", 1938) (Box 2, Folder 95)
- Baxter, Allen, (2) (1935) (Box 2, Folder 96)
- Baxter, Anne (2) (Box 2, Folder 97)
- Baxter, Gladys (Box 2, Folder 98)
- Baxter, Jane (1935) (Box 2, Folder 99)
- Baxter, Warner (13) (1929,1932,1937) (Box 2, Folder 100)
- The Beachcombers (Box 2, Folder 101)
- Beal, John (1938) (Box 2, Folder 102)
- Beery, Noah (3), (1 o.s.) (Box 2, Folder 103)
- Beery, Wallace (18, 1 autograph) (1935,1937), (1 o.s.) (Box 2, Folder 104)
- Beery, William (Box 2, Folder 105)
- Behan, Brendan (Box 2, Folder 106)
- Bekassy, Stephen (Box 2, Folder 107)
- Belafonte, Harry (11) (Box 2, Folder 108)
- Belasco, David (1 o.s., signed to Joe Laurie) (Box 2, Folder 109)
- Bell, Adelaide (1 o.s.signed) (Box 2, Folder 110)
- Bell, Rex (1932) (Box 2, Folder 111)
- Bellamy, Madge (Box 2, Folder 112)
- Bellamy, Ralph (6) (1936,1937) (Box 2, Folder 113)
- Bendix, William (4) (Box 2, Folder 114)
- Bennett, Constance (7) (1936,1937), (4 o.s., 2 signed) (Box 2, Folder 115)
- Bennett, Edna (signed?) (Box 2, Folder 116)
- Bennett, Enid (Box 2, Folder 117)
- Bennett, Joan (15) (1932,1935,1936,1937,1938), (1 o.s.) (Box 2, Folder 118)
- Bennett, Richard (3, 1 signed)(1931) (Box 2, Folder 119)
- Benny, Jack (13) (1936,1940) (Box 2, Folder 120)
- Bergen, Candice (3) (Box 2, Folder 121)
- Bergen, Edgar & Charlie McCarthy (11) (Box 2, Folder 122)
- Bergman, Ingrid, (1 o.s.) (Box 2, Folder 123)
- Berkeley, Anne (Box 2, Folder 124)
- Bernard, Sam (1 o.s., signed to Joe Laurie) (Box 2, Folder 125)
- Bernie, Ben (Box 2, Folder 126)
- Besser, Joe (Box 2, Folder 127)
- Best, Edna (1935) (Box 2, Folder 128)
- Bickford, Charles (4) (Box 2, Folder 129)
- Blair, Janet (Box 2, Folder 130)
- Blane, Sally (autograph) (Box 2, Folder 131)
- Blinn, Holbrook, (1 o.s.) (Box 2, Folder 132)
- Bliss, Helena (3) (Box 2, Folder 133)
- Bliss, Herbert (Box 2, Folder 134)
- Blondell, Joan (20) (1937, 1937) (Box 2, Folder 135)
- Blondell, Mabel, (1 o.s.) (Box 2, Folder 136)
- Blue, Ben (1937) (Box 2, Folder 137)
- Boardman, Eleanor (2) (1932) (Box 2, Folder 138)
- Boardman, Virginia (1928) (Box 2, Folder 139)
- Bogart, Humphrey (2) (1936) (Box 2, Folder 140)
- Boland, Mary (6) (1934,1936) (Box 2, Folder 141)
- Bolender, Todd (2) (Box 2, Folder 142)
- Boles, John (5) (1936), (2 o.s., 1 signed) (Box 2, Folder 143)
- Bolm, Adolph (2) (Box 2, Folder 144)
- Bonanova, Fortunio(2 o.s.) (Box 2, Folder 145)
- Booth, Josephine (Box 2, Folder 146)
- Bordoni, Irene (2) (Box 2, Folder 147)
- Borge, Victor (9) (Box 2, Folder 148)
- Boswell, Connee (2) (1944) (Box 2, Folder 149)
- Bosworth, Hobart (3, 1 signature) (Box 2, Folder 150)
- Boulting, John (Box 2, Folder 151)
- Bowe, Morton (2) (Box 2, Folder 152)
- Bowers, Kenny (Box 2, Folder 153)
- Bow, Clara (12)(1928,1936), (2 o.s.) (Box 2, Folder 154)
- Boyd, William (10) (1929) (Box 3, Folder 155)
- Boyer, Charles (4) (1936), (1 o.s.) (Box 3, Folder 156)
- Bradley, Grace (4) (1934, 1936) (Box 3, Folder 157)
- Brady, Alice (7, 1 signed)(1933,1934,1935) (Box 3, Folder 158)
- Brandon, Dolores (Box 3, Folder 159)
- Brasseur, Claude (1968) (Box 3, Folder 160)
- Brault, Denis (Box 3, Folder 161)
- Bray, CE, (signed, 1922) (Box 3, Folder 162)
- Bredlon, Charles (Box 3, Folder 163)
- Breen, Bobby and Slickie (sea lion) (6)(1937,1939) (Box 3, Folder 164)
- Breese, Edmund (1936, signed to Joe Laurie) (Box 3, Folder 165)
- Brennan, Helen (2, 1 signed) (Box 3, Folder 166)
- Brennan, Walter (2) (1936) (Box 3, Folder 167)
- Brent, Evelyn (2, 1 autograph) (Box 3, Folder 168)
- Brent, George (7) (1934, 1936) (Box 3, Folder 169)
- Brewster, Gloria (Box 3, Folder 170)
- Brian, Mary (2) (Box 3, Folder 171)
- Briansky (Box 3, Folder 172)
- Brice, Fanny (7, 2 signed, 1941,1943) (Box 3, Folder 173)
- Brisson, Carl (1934) (Box 3, Folder 174)
- Britton, Pamela 2) (1953) (Box 3, Folder 175)
- Brockwell, Gladys (2)(1916?,1920) (Box 3, Folder 176)
  (w/Eve Southern & Kate Price)
- Broderick, Helen (1937) (Box 3, Folder 177)
- Brokenshire, Norman, (1 o.s.) (Box 3, Folder 178)
- Brook, Clive (2) (1932) (Box 3, Folder 179)
- Brotherson, Eric (Box 3, Folder 180)
- Brown, Barbara (Box 3, Folder 181)
- Brown, Clarence (Box 3, Folder 182)
- Brown, Joe E(20), (1934,1937) (w/Lillian Bond) (Box 3, Folder 183)
- Brown, Johnny Mack (5) (1929, 1931) (Box 3, Folder 184)
- Brown, Tom (3)(1935, 1937) (Box 3, Folder 185)
- Bruce, Virginia (30) (1929,1930,1935,1936), (2 o.s.) (Box 3, Folder 186)
- Bryan, Jane, (1 o.s.) (Box 3, Folder 187)
- Buck and Bubbles (Box 3, Folder 188)
- Buckler, John (1934) (Box 3, Folder 189)
- Buckmaster, John (Box 3, Folder 190)
- Buka, Donald (Box 3, Folder 191)
- Burke, Billie (6, 2 signed, 1931 [David Suransky],1947) (1935,1941,1947), (2 o.s.) (Box 3, Folder 192)
- Burke, Minnie (1939), (note on back to Frankie Bailey from "Otis" (Box 3, Folder 193)
- Burns, Bob (16)(1936,1937,1939), (w/Martha Raye) (Box 3, Folder 194)
- Burns, George (8) (1935,1936) (Box 3, Folder 195)
- Burnson, George (Box 3, Folder 196)
- Burr, Donald (2) (Box 3, Folder 197)
- Burton, Richard (signed) (Box 3, Folder 198)
- Burton, Robert (Box 3, Folder 199)
- Bushman, Francis (1915), signed (Box 3, Folder 200)
- Bushman, Ralph (Box 3, Folder 201)
- Butler, Edward (Box 3, Folder 202)
- Butterworth, Charles (2) (Box 3, Folder 203)
- Buzzell, Eddie (1929) (Box 3, Folder 204)
- Cabot, Bruce (3) (1934) (Box 3, Folder 205)
- Caccialanza, Gisella (Box 3, Folder 206)
- Cagney, James (9) (1933,1935) (Box 3, Folder 207)
- Cagney, Jean (2) (1939) (Box 3, Folder 208)
- Calhern, Louis (Box 3, Folder 209)
- California Collegians (1 o.s., signed, 1927) (Box 3, Folder 210)
- Callahan, Margaret (Box 3, Folder 211)
- Calleia, Joseph (3) (Box 3, Folder 212)
- Calvert, Catherine (1928) (Box 3, Folder 213)
- Cameron, Grace (16, 5 signed: 1904,1918,1920,1946) (Box 3, Folder 214)
- Cameron, Madeline (Box 3, Folder 215)
- Campbell, Louise (1938) (Box 3, Folder 216)
- Campbell, Sadie (Box 3, Folder 217)
- Campbell, Vicki (Box 3, Folder 218)
- Cansino, Rita (1935,1936) (Box 3, Folder 219)
- Cantor, Eddie (14, plus "E.C.'s Picture Book",4 pp, folds, out to poster) (Box 3, Folder 220)
  (1935,1937)
- Carlisle, Kitty (9)(1934) (Box 3, Folder 221)
- Carlisle, Mary (11) (1936,1937) (Box 3, Folder 222)
- Carlson, Richard (2) (1939) (Box 3, Folder 223)
- Carney, Art (1968) (Box 3, Folder 224)
- Carol, Sue, (1 o.s.) (Box 3, Folder 225)
- Carr, Alexander (Box 3, Folder 226)
- Carradine, John (3) (1936) (Box 3, Folder 227)
- Carrillo, Leo ("The Cisco Kid")(13,1 signed)(1935,1936,1937) (Box 3, Folder 228)
- Carroll, Leo (2) (3 o.s.) (Box 3, Folder 229)
- Carroll, Nancy (7)(1931), (1 o.s.) (Box 3, Folder 230)
- Carroll, Madeleine (18)(1936,1937,1939,1941 (Selznick,David) (Box 3, Folder 231)
- Cassel, Walter (8) (Box 3, Folder 232)
- Castle, Don (Box 3, Folder 233)
- Cavanagh, Paul (1938) (Box 3, Folder 234)
- Chamberlain, Birdie (Box 3, Folder 235)
- Chaney, Lon (4, 1 autograph) (Box 4, Folder 236)
- Channing, Carol (2) (Box 4, Folder 237)
- Chaplin, Charlie (44, 1 autograph)(Paulette Goddard, Gandhi) (1918,1926,1927,1929,1931,1933 (Box 4, Folder 238)
- Chase, Charley (2) (Box 4, Folder 239)
- Chatterton, Ruth (5,1 autograph) (1933) (Box 4, Folder 240)
- Chevalier, Maurice (9, 1 autograph) (1935), (1 o.s.) (Box 4, Folder 241)
- Christians, Mady (2) (Box 4, Folder 242)
- Churchill, Marguerite (stamped autograph) (Box 4, Folder 243)
- Ciccolini, Guido (signed, 1915, to H.H. Campbell) (Box 4, Folder 244)
- Claire, Ina (3, 1 signed) (Box 4, Folder 245)
- Clark, Bobby (1 photo, 1 drawing by Barney Fagan) (Box 4, Folder 246)
- Clark, Janet Elsie (signed, to Frankie Bailey) (Box 4, Folder 247)
- Clark, Mae (5 photos, + 1 nitrate negative)(1935,1937) (Box 4, Folder 248)
- Clayton, Ethel (Box 4, Folder 249)
- Clayton, Jan (Box 4, Folder 250)
- Clive, Colin (Box 4, Folder 251)
- Cloony, Rosemary (signed) (Box 4, Folder 252)
- Clou, May (Box 4, Folder 253)
- Clyde, Jane (2, 1 autograph)(1930), (1 o.s.) (Box 4, Folder 254)
- Cobos, Antonia (Box 4, Folder 255)
- Coca, Imogene (1968-69) (Box 4, Folder 256)
- Cochran, Steve (Box 4, Folder 257)
- Cody, William F. ("Buffalo Bill")(2 photos, + 24 pp. booklet "Buffalo Bill (Himself) and 101 Ranch Wild West") (Box 4, Folder 258)
- Cohan, George M (Box 4, Folder 259)
- Colbert, Claudette (34)(1927,1934,1935,1936,1937,1939,1940) (Box 4, Folder 260)
- Collins, Charles (Box 4, Folder 261)
- Collins, Cora Sue(2) (Box 4, Folder 262)
- Collins, Eddie (Box 4, Folder 263)
- Colman, Ronald (11)(1935,1936), (1 o.s.) (Box 4, Folder 264)
- Colt, Ethel B (Ethel Barrymore)(1932) (Box 4, Folder 265)
- Colt, Samuel Barrymore (Box 4, Folder 266)
- Compson, Betty (2, 1 autograph) (Box 4, Folder 267)
- Conklin, Chester (4) (1928) (Box 4, Folder 268)
- Conolly, Walter (1936) (Box 4, Folder 269)
- Coogan, Jackie (15, 7 signed, Mr & Mrs. H.G. Meyer) (1931) (Box 4, Folder 270)
- Cook, Donald (1942?) (Box 4, Folder 271)
- Cooper, Ben (1959) (Box 4, Folder 272)
- Cooper, Gary (34, 1 signed)(1911-15?,1929,1934,1935,1936), (1 o.s.) (Box 4, Folder 273)
- Cooper, Gladys (Box 4, Folder 274)
- Cooper, Jackie (21)(1935) (Box 4, Folder 275)
- Cooper, Melville (Box 4, Folder 276)
- Corday, Marcelle (Box 4, Folder 277)
- Corey, Wendell (Box 4, Folder 278)
- Cornell, Katherine (7, 1 signed to W[?] Bartmann), (2 o.s., 1 signed) (Box 4, Folder 279)
- Cortez, Ricardo (Box 4, Folder 280)
- Costello, Diosa (Box 4, Folder 281)
- Costello, Dolores (Box 4, Folder 282)
- Cotton, Joseph (Box 4, Folder 283)
- Coward, Noel (4) (1933, 1935) (Box 4, Folder 284)
- Cowl, Jane (2, signed) (Box 4, Folder 285)
- Craig, Helen (Box 4, Folder 286)
- Craven, Frank (2) (1942) (Box 4, Folder 287)
- Crawford, Dorothy (3) (Box 4, Folder 288)
- Crawford, Joan (45, 1 signed) (1929,1936,1944), (4 o.s.) (Box 4, Folder 289)
- Cromwell, Richard (Box 4, Folder 290)
- Crosby, Bing (23)(1934,1935,1936,1937,1938,1940) (Box 4, Folder 291)
- Cruze, James, (1 o.s.) (Box 4, Folder 292)
- Cullen, James H(signed March 1916) (Box 4, Folder 293)
- Cummings, Robert (4, 1941) (Box 4, Folder 294)
- Cunningham, Merce (see Martha Graham) (Box 4, Folder 295)
- Curtis, Alan (Box 4, Folder 296)
- Curtwright, Jorja (Box 4, Folder 297)
- Cushman, Wilbur (Box 4, Folder 298)
- Dailey, Dan (1968-69) (Box 4, Folder 299)
- Dale, James (Box 4, Folder 300)
- Dalton, Dorothy (Box 4, Folder 301)
- Daly, Blythe (1 o.s., signed) (Box 4, Folder 302)
- Damita, Lily (4)(1931) (Box 4, Folder 303)
- Dana, Leora (3) (Box 4, Folder 304)
- Dandridge, Ruby (Box 4, Folder 305)
- Dane, Karl (Box 4, Folder 306)
- Daniel, Henry (Box 4, Folder 307)
- Daniels, Bebe (6, 1 autograph)(1933) (Box 4, Folder 308)
- Danilova, Alexandra (4) (Box 4, Folder 309)
- Darrieux, Danielle (7)(1938) (Box 5, Folder 310)
- Dauphin, Claude (Box 5, Folder 311)
- Davenport, Henry (2, both signed: July 1926) (Box 5, Folder 312)
- Davidson, Bill (Box 5, Folder 313)
- Davies, Marion (16) (1928,1929,1933,1935,1936), (1 o.s.) (Box 5, Folder 314)
- Davis, Bette (10)(1935,1936) (Box 5, Folder 315)
- Davis, Roger (photo of drawing, initials "D F") (Box 5, Folder 316)
- Davis, Sammy, Jr (2) (Box 5, Folder 317)
- Daw, Marjorie (Box 5, Folder 318)
- Dawson, Doris (Box 5, Folder 319)
- Day, Lorraine (4) (Box 5, Folder 320)
- Day, Marceline (Box 5, Folder 321)
- Dayton, June (Box 5, Folder 322)
- Dean, Priscilla (autograph) (Box 5, Folder 323)
- De Angelis, Jefferson (signed, Mar 9 1920) (Box 5, Folder 324)
- De Camp, Rosemary (1938) (Box 5, Folder 325)
- Dee, Francis (5)(1931,1934,1935) (Box 5, Folder 326)
- De Havilland, Olivia (9)(1935,1936,1937,1938), (1 o.s.) (Box 5, Folder 327)
- De La Motte, Marguerite (Box 5, Folder 328)
- Del Rio, Dolores (11)(1928,1934,1935,1936) (Box 5, Folder 329)
- De Mille, Katharine (5)(1935,1936) (Box 5, Folder 330)
- Dennis, Bridget (Box 5, Folder 331)
- Denny, Reginald (3)(1935,1936) (Box 5, Folder 332)
- De Osuna, Chato (Box 5, Folder 333)
- De Rache, Charles (Box 5, Folder 334)
- Derwant, Clarence (3) (Box 5, Folder 335)
- Devine, Andy (8)(1936,1937,1943), (postcard addressed to Harriette Stark, 1970) (Box 5, Folder 336)
- De Voe, Daisy (2) (Box 5, Folder 337)
- Diamond, Leo (3) (Box 5, Folder 338)
- Dickson, Gloria (5) (Box 5, Folder 339)
- Dietrich, Marlene (10)(1934,1935,1937) (Box 5, Folder 340)
- Digges, Dudley (signed, to Walter Bartmann) (Box 5, Folder 341)
- Dingle, Charles (1941) (Box 5, Folder 342)
- The Dionne Quintuplets (16)(1936) (Box 5, Folder 343)
- Dix, Richard (11)(1934,1935,1936) (Box 5, Folder 344)
- Dixon, Audrey (Box 5, Folder 345)
- Dja, Devi (Box 5, Folder 346)
- Dockstader, Lew (Box 5, Folder 347)
- Donahue, Troy (6) (Box 5, Folder 348)
- Donat, Robert (8,1 signed)(1935) (Box 5, Folder 349)
- Donovan, King (1968-69) (Box 5, Folder 350)
- Dorey, Alice (autograph) (Box 5, Folder 351)
- Dorne, Cyrilla (signed, to "Donette", 1939) (Box 5, Folder 352)
- Dorsay, Fifi (2)(1931) (Box 5, Folder 353)
- Douglas, Melvyn (5, 1 autograph)(1937) (Box 5, Folder 354)
- Dove, Billie (5) (Box 5, Folder 355)
- Dowling, Eddie (Box 5, Folder 356)
- Downey, Morton (Box 5, Folder 357)
- Drake, Alfred (Box 5, Folder 358)
- Drake, Frances (Box 5, Folder 359)
- Draper, Paul (3) (Box 5, Folder 360)
- Draper, Ruth (3, 1 autograph, 1937) (Box 5, Folder 361)
- Dresser, Louise (3) (Box 5, Folder 362)
- Dressler, Marie (28)(1890,1908,1921,1930,1931), (2 o.s., 1 signed) (Box 5, Folder 363)
- Drew, Ellen (Box 5, Folder 364)
- Drew, John (2) (Box 5, Folder 365)
- Duffy, Henry (Box 5, Folder 366)
- Dumke, Ralph (Box 5, Folder 367)
- Duncan, William (Box 5, Folder 368)
- The Duncan sisters (Rosetta and Vivian) (4, 1 signed) (1926,1929), (2 o.s., 1 signed) (Box 5, Folder 369)
- Dunham, Katherine (5) (Box 5, Folder 370)
- Dunn, James (6)(1936,1937) (Box 5, Folder 371)
- Dunne, Irene (15)(1936,1939) (Box 5, Folder 372)
- Dunning, Edwin (Box 5, Folder 373)
- Duncan, Raymond (Box 5, Folder 374)
- Duprez, June (1938) (Box 5, Folder 375)
- Durante, James (5)(1935,1936) (Box 5, Folder 376)
- Duranty, Walter (Box 5, Folder 377)
- Durbin, Deanna (15) (1936,1937,1938) (Box 5, Folder 378)
- Dvorak, Ann (6)(1933,1934) (Box 5, Folder 379)
- Eastwood, Clint (The Good, the Bad, and the Ugly) (Box 5, Folder 380)
- Ebsen, Buddy (4)(1935,1936,1937) (Box 5, Folder 381)
- Eckles, Robert (Box 5, Folder 382)
- Eddy, Helen Jerome (signed, to "Mr. Fountain") (Box 5, Folder 383)
- Eddy, Nelson (18)(1933,1936), (1 o.s.) (Box 5, Folder 384)
- Edeson, Robert (Box 6, Folder 385)
- Edwards, Cliff (Box 6, Folder 386)
- Edwards, Gus (3)(1929) (Box 6, Folder 387)
- Edwards, Jimmy (Box 6, Folder 388)
- Edwards, Vince (Box 6, Folder 389)
- Eglevsky, Andre (5) (Box 6, Folder 390)
- Ehrhardt, Bess (3) (Box 6, Folder 391)
- Eilers, Sally (2) (Box 6, Folder 392)
- Elder, Ruth (2)(1929) (Box 6, Folder 393)
- Ellis, Mary (1936) (Box 6, Folder 394)
- Eltinge, Julian (16, 6 signed)(1911,1912-13,1936) (Box 6, Folder 395)
- Emerson, Faye (signed, to Mrs. C. W. Wren) (Box 6, Folder 396)
- Enters, Angna (2) (Box 6, Folder 397)
- Erhard, Jan (Box 6, Folder 398)
- Ericson, John (Box 6, Folder 399)
- Errol, Leon (2) (1943) (Box 6, Folder 400)
- Errolle, Martha (4) (Box 6, Folder 401)
- Erway, Ben (Box 6, Folder 402)
- Erwin, Stuart (7)(1936,1937) (Box 6, Folder 403)
- Essen, Viola (see Ivan Kirore) (Box 6, Folder 404)
- Evans, Madge (26)(1935) (Box 6, Folder 405)
- Evans, Maurice (3, 2 signed)(1945) (Box 6, Folder 406)
- Evans, Wilbur (3)(1933) (Box 6, Folder 407)
- Evelyn, Judith (Box 6, Folder 408)
- Fabran, Nanette (1940) (Box 6, Folder 409)
- Fair, Elinor (signed, to LaVerne) (Box 6, Folder 410)
- Fairbanks, Douglas (5)(1933,1936), (1 o.s.) (Box 6, Folder 411)
- Fairbanks, Douglas Jr. (signed, to J---?) (Box 6, Folder 412)
- Farmer, Frances (3) (Box 6, Folder 413)
- Farnum, Franklyn (signed, to "Dave") (Box 6, Folder 414)
- Farnum, William (Box 6, Folder 415)
- Farrell, Charles (5) (1929,1931,1934), (1 o.s.) (Box 6, Folder 416)
- Farrell, Glenda (5) (Box 6, Folder 417)
- Fazeuda, Louise (4, 1 autograph postcard: postmarked 1970) (Box 6, Folder 418)
- Faversham, William(2, both signed to Frank Allen, 1924,1927) (Box 6, Folder 419)
- Fay, Frank (2) (Box 6, Folder 420)
- Faye, Alice (8)(1937) (Box 6, Folder 421)
- Faye, Julia (1952) (Box 6, Folder 422)
- Fears, Peggy (signed, to "Sam") (Box 6, Folder 423)
- Fenn, Jean (Box 6, Folder 424)
- Ferguson, Elsie (2, 1 signed? 1909), (1 o.s.) (Box 6, Folder 425)
- Ferguson, Helen (Box 6, Folder 426)
- Feusier, Norman (Box 6, Folder 427)
- Field, Virginia (10)(1937) (Box 6, Folder 428)
- Fielding, Margaret (2)(1932) (Box 6, Folder 429)
- Fields, Eleanor (and her wonderful dog Teddy, Max Sennett Comedies) (Box 6, Folder 430)
- Fields, Gracie (1945) (Box 6, Folder 431)
- Fields, W.C. (William Clay) (18, 1 signed, to "Jackson, N.M.") (1933, 1935, 1936, 1937, 1943, 1944) (Box 6, Folder 432)
- Finch, Flora (Box 6, Folder 433)
- Fiske, Mrs. Minnie Madden (1 o.s., signed) (Box 6, Folder 434)
- Fitzgerald, Barry (Box 6, Folder 435)
- Fleeson, Neville (2, both signed to "Sam") (Box 6, Folder 436)
- Fleming, Una (Box 6, Folder 437)
- Fonda, Henry (6) (1935) (Box 6, Folder 438)
- Fontaine, Claribel (2) (Box 6, Folder 439)
- Fontaine, Joan (5) (1937), (1 o.s.) (Box 6, Folder 440)
- Fontanne, Lynn (6, 1 signed, "for the Thomas H. Lindsay Collection, April 7, 1943"), (1931) (Box 6, Folder 441)
- Foran, Nick (Box 6, Folder 442)
- Forbes, Ralph (3) (Box 6, Folder 443)
- Forbes-Robertson, Sir J., (1 o.s.) (Box 6, Folder 444)
- Ford, Glenn (Gwyllyn) (2, 1 signed to "Wess and Christine") (Box 6, Folder 445)
- Ford, Wallace (5) (1936) (Box 6, Folder 446)
- Forrest, Helen (signed, to "John") (Box 6, Folder 447)
- Foster, Norman (3) (Box 6, Folder 448)
- Foster, Preston (5) (1936, 1937) (Box 6, Folder 449)
- Fowley, Douglas (1935) (Box 6, Folder 450)
- Frances, Alec (Box 6, Folder 451)
- Francis, Kay (16) (1930, 1935), (1 o.s.) (Box 6, Folder 452)
- Frawley, William (2) (1934) (Box 6, Folder 453)
- Frazier, Robert (Box 6, Folder 454)